In the window of the drawing, double-click to open the Previous Files folder.
Find the C, Simulation, Instability, Layered Patterns, and the Gizmo Tool.
Find the C, Simulation, Instability, Layered Patterns, and the Gizmo Tool in the double-click or double-click window of the 2D or 3D window.
When the 3D window is not correctly arranged in the 3D window, there is a high possibility that the simulation will not be stable.
In addition, there needs to be enough space between the layers of the panel to prevent conflicts when the panel is simulated, so the panel needs to be rearranged.
In the 2D window,
In the window, select the 3D window panel.
On the 3D window panel, right-click and select Rearrange 2D Arrangement in the menu.
Select Rearrange the position of the 3D panel.
Use the positioning tool to arrange the layers between the 3D panels.
Now, if you want to rearrange the layers, select the 3D panel.
Use the positioning tool to navigate the layers from the 3D panel to the 3D panel.
Turn on the fire to simulate the effect after adjustment
and adjust the length according to the output
I discuss it again after spreading
Now it remains to install the todos
Now it is working
than it was before